Did we have someone that
pretty at our academy?
So elegant...
That girl is so beautiful.
Your big sister?
I can't find my big sister!
Then why don't we look for her together?
Really?
My name is Lily White.
And you are?
My name is Tiana Algren!
Algren?
Lily?
It's nothing.
Let's go find your big sister together.
Yes!
She looked over here!
So noble!
So heartwarming!
Ahh!
Amazing...
Lovely...
Maybe I overdid it a bit.
It's my sister!
Big sister!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 7
The Girl Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Infiltrates a Sorcery Academy
Thank you for looking
after my little sister.
Not at all.
Tiana's such a well-behaved little girl.
I haven't introduced myself.
I'm Ariane Algren.
My name is Lily White.
I see, so you're Miss Lily?
Yes.
Why don't I get straight to the point?
You're not one of our students, are you?
No, I'm...
You're very clever, Lady Ariane.
I try to be capable in all things.
Then what academy do you attend?
I will neither run nor hide,
so why don't you also tell the truth?
Then I shall do that.
I'm sorry to have deceived you.
My name is Ray White, and I attend
the Arnold Academy of Sorcery.
It's nice to meet you.
Wait, wait. What. What?
Is everything all right?
You're a boy?!
Yes?
N-Now just one moment,
because your your body structure and
muscle tone are unmistakably female...
And then your voice!
What did you do to your voice?
It's an application of inside
code and a bit of sorcery.
Application?
But Ray White...
I believe that's the name of the very
first ordinary to attend the academy.
They say you are quite
accomplished in battle.
I can't believe that rumor
reached even your academy.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Your appearance and your
voice are so mismatched,
my head's starting to spin.
I admit I was taken aback,
but it doesn't change the fact
that you helped my little sister.
I could never stain the Algren name by
having you leave without a gift of gratitude.
Why don't I show you what
they call royal style?
Good luck to you both!
I thank you for the proposed
mock battle, Miss Algren.
Please call me Ariane.
Are you sure? We did just meet.
I'm making a special exception.
Then, I am much obliged.
I'd like you to call me Ray, as well.
Once again, it's nice to meet you.
The pleasure is mine, Ariane.
Could you change your voice back?
That discrepancy is just...
Oh.
Understood.
That was spectacular, Ariane.
My big sister is amazing!
You're welcome.
Bye-bye! See you later!
Bye-bye!
Tiana is such a good kid.
I'm sure she will grow up to be
an elegant and beautiful person who
is loved by all, just like you.
What is it?
N-Nothing at all!
Are you always saying things
like that to girls?
I've been taught to always compliment women.
You really are strange.
Really?
You will not be participating
in the Magic Chevalier?
For multiple reasons.
Right now I am a member
of the organizational staff,
but I also help my friend train.
A friend?
It's Amelia.
Amelia?
Do you mean Amelia Rose?
Yes.
So you came all the way here for her?
That's right.
So I guess she was able to
make a friend like you.
She is getting strong.
She will win first place
in the rookie bracket.
You are going to learn
what defeat tastes like.
I look forward to that.
It's gotten really late.
Are you all right?
I-I'm so sorry!
I...
Are you hurt?
Is something wrong?
I-I'm fine!
Thank you so much!
Not at all.
It would be tragic if
your snow white skin was marred.
Goodbye, then.
Oh?
W-Won't you please tell me your name?
My name is Lily White.
Big Sister Lily!
And your name is?
I-I'm Maria Bradley.
Bradley...?
Are you Rebecca's younger sister?
You know my older sister?
I do.
Rebecca has helped me out greatly.
I... I was having doubts about coming
to this school, but not anymore!
If you're here, I will definitely
enroll next year!
Please wait for me!
Is that so?
Then, I'll be going now.
I'm looking forward to seeing you again.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Private Amelia!
Looks like you're working hard!
Ranger!
Reporting for another day of training!
Thank you, Eris and Claris!
But, Amelia, make sure you stay focused.
That voice...
Ray?
Why is Ray's voice coming
from that beautiful girl?
Oh, sorry.
I just came back from my mission.
It's me.
What?!
Look at that! It's so amazing!
The scenery is so beautiful.
You seem to be having fun today.
Well, obviously!
Seriously, that training is hell.
But, I am really nervous.
N-No-Not me!
Don't worry.
My master is a good person.
Have you been well, Ray?!
Have you gotten even taller?
You always say that, but I haven't.
Yeah, you're right.
So are these them?
Yes. My irreplaceable friends
I met at the academy.
I'm Evi Armstrong.
Ray and I share a dorm room and
we've gotten really close.
I'm Lydia Ainsworth.
But hmm...
You're big.
You can tell?
Keep it up.
And I'd like you to become
good friends with Ray.
Naturally!
I'm... I'm Elisa Griffith.
I'm a half-elf.
I see.
You're big, too, in another sense.
Huh?
I like how adorably clueless you are.
Um, well. Erm...
I'm a huge fan of your work!
May I... May I have your autograph?
Carla, do you have a pen?
Yes. Right here.
M-My name is Claris Cleveland.
Ugh, why...
I heard you want to become a hunter.
How do you know that?
I know the head of the Cleveland house.
He came to me for advice a while back.
Oh, really?
I'm a platinum hunter.
Unfortunately, now I'm like this.
That's the first time I've seen a real one.
With that said,
there's no reason why you
can't become a hunter,
just because you're a girl or the
daughter of a noble house.
What's important is taking that first step.
I'm Amelia Rose. It's been a long time.
Yes, we've met each other at a few parties.
Yes.
I'd like to talk to you in private.
Come this way.
O-Of course.
Master Ray,
could you please help me?
I heard something rather concerning.
They say that the Empire's angels
of death have started moving again.
The Grim Reapers.
What is the Aywell Empire's
death squad up to?
I haven't heard that much.
But the timing does concern me.
You mean the Magic Chevalier?
That's right.
All of the noble families will
come together for that event.
Please keep that in mind.
Understood.
You seem worried about something.
Isn't that so, Amelia Rose?
What do you mean?
These are letters from Ray.
At first, he was just reporting his status.
But lately... well.
Well... what?
He knows that you have hidden
something away in your heart,
but apparently, he doesn't know if
he is allowed to find out what.
You know about Ray's past, correct?
I do.
He has talent.
He's the world's best sorcerer,
and easily surpasses me.
I've taught him as much
sorcery knowledge as I can,
but there was one thing that
I could not teach him.
The human heart.
The human... heart.
When I first met Ray,
he was like a kid who had given
up on everything in this world.
It took some time,
but we managed to get him back bit by bit.
But even then, the only people
around him then were us soldiers.
That's why I recommended
that he join the academy.
I hoped that there,
he could develop his heart and
find himself valuable friends.
And today, you all came.
Ray is worried about you.
He's picking up on subtle
clues about human emotions.
That makes me so incredibly happy.
Miss Lydia...
Amelia Rose.
I don't know what you have in your heart.
Nobody does, except for you.
You are welcome to keep what is in it
a secret for the rest of your life.
But if you really wish to change yourself,
trust your friends.
Please trust in him.
All right, everyone!
Change into your swimsuits!
I've been waiting for this.
We're going swimming, Ray!
Yay!
Today was a lot of fun.
Thanks for inviting me.
Knowing you enjoyed it is
all the thanks I need.
Lydia is a good person and
Carla's cuisine was delicious.
No complaints here!
But...
I wasn't expecting Miss Abbie
and Carol to show up.
That was... amazing.
She's getting there.
Ray, in your letters you asked what
you ought to do about Amelia.
Like I did for you,
do what you can for her.
Whatever you yourself want to do for her.
I will, Master.
Roll call!
One!
Good, everyone's here!
This day has finally come.
Private Amelia, let me reward you
with the highest of compliments.
Ranger!
Thank you!
And now we will commence with the final
examination of the Ainsworth-style boot camp!
Ranger!
If you manage to pass the exam,
I shall grant you this Ranger badge.
Now, Private Amelia,
make the petals of the
rose on my chest scatter!
Don't worry.
I won't unleash my powers.
Amelia, I know how strong you are.
Ray...
Let the examination begin!
Ranger!
And here we are at this
year's Magic Chevalier.
All of you who stand before me are brave
fighters who have fought to be here,
and to ultimately attain the glory of
being the strongest student sorcerer.
If you want to master sorcery,
it requires not just talent and hard work,
but also an environment where
healthy competition is fostered.
This tournament is certainly going
to be a good stepping stone for you.
I hope that you will give
it everything you have.
With this, I proclaim the
Magic Chevalier open!
Amelia.
Ariane.
It's been a while since we spoke like this.
That's true.
You seem to have changed a bit.
You think so?
It seems that I really
wasn't the right one...
Huh?
I'll be waiting for you in the final round.
Right. We'll meet again in the final round.
And just like that,
it's time for the semi-finals of the
Magic Chevalier's rookie bracket!
I, Dina Sera, will continue
to provide live coverage.
As a commentator, I have Miss
Carol Caroline with me.
Wink!
And now, let me introduce our competitors.
From the Mercross Academy of
Sorcery, Shine Girard.
From the Arnold Academy of Sorcery, Amelia Rose.
Amelia!
You got this!
Good luck!
Show them, Amelia!
Good luck, Amelia.
I, Abbie Garnet, will be
acting as the referee.
A player wins when they have pushed
their opponent out of the ring,
or if they scatter the rose
from the other participant's chest.
The match can also be ended if I determine
that the bout should not go on.
Are you both ready?
I am.
Come get it!
Begin!
It's over!
The winner is Amelia Rose!
Th-The match is over!
Amazingly, Rose only needed one
spell to deliver the deciding blow!
That was a well-executed delay.
The moment the match began,
Amelia planted an activated
spell in the ground.
Then she just needed to
lure her prey over it,
and boom!
That is some very difficult
sorcery right there,
so it's amazing how well
Amelia pulled it off!
Yes!
Wow!
She just crushed him.
There's no doubt that she'll win it all!
Where are you going, Ray?
I have some organization staff work to do.
Ray.
It's time, Albert.
I see.
I wish you a good fight.
Yeah, I'm off.
Next up, we have a match between
the Diom Academy of Sorcery's Ariane Algren
and the Arnold Academy
of Sorcery's Albert Alium.
Ariane! Ariane! Ariane!
Go! Fight!
Begin!
Impressive sword play from both sides!
This is a straight clash of power on power!
And now the match has shifted
heavily to one side.
I suppose this is what you can expect
from the eldest daughter of
the great house of Algren.
Probably!
Al...
You won't surrender?
It would be dangerous to continue.
I'm well aware.
The old me would have
given up a long time ago.
But you know...
Once we are aware,
we can start anything over.
You're the only one who can provide
yourself with the answer you seek.
...my heart will not accept defeat!
Got you!
Prepare yourself!
Lightning Strike!
It's over!
The winner is Ariane Algren.
And the match is over!
With an overwhelming blow,
Algren has secured her victory.
It was literally a show of force!
I can't wait for the final round!
I'm bursting with excitement.
Oh.
I didn't even notice how
beautiful the sky is today.
Was that for real?
So she's going to be
fighting against Amelia?
M-Miss Caroline, what are you doing?!
Hello, spectators!
I'll be singing a song to get us all
in the mood for the final round.
You know, I also have
nights when I get lonely.
I know what you mean, Abbie.
Oh, where is Miss Carol?
Erryone, let's just cut loose!
This is bad! Everyone run!
Are you all okay?!
Don't look!
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
This is the preview of the next episode
of The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World!
Amelia's heart wavers in light
of Ariane's overwhelming power!
But life is never considerate and
brings in an unexpected guest.
"The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest
Sorcerer Inspires the Rose"!
Episode 8
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer Inspires the Rose
This was Carol Caroline. Wink!